https://www.3wishes.com/privacy-security/

Shop Cyber Monday Deals! Limited Supply!
Check Back Often For Even More Sexy Deals!
Home
Privacy / Security
Privacy / Security
Privacy & Security Policy GovernanceThis Privacy & Security Policy governs the manner in which 3WISHES.COM, Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the https://www.3wishes.com/ or “website”. This privacy policy applies to the website and all products and services offered by 3WISHES.COM, Inc. (3WISHES.COM).The Privacy & Security Policy is to inform users of:• What personal information is collected from users through the website, how it is used, and with whom it is shared.• How a user can correct, alter, or delete their information from the website.• The security controls in place to safeguard against misuse of user information.• 3WISHES.COM Safe Shopping Guarantee Policy.
Privacy
Collection of Information: 3WISHES.COM will not collect any personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information by visiting our website anonymously, except that it may prevent users from engaging in certain website related activities.
We may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, register a website account, place an order, fill out a form response to a survey, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our website. For 3WISHES.COM to process your order we must obtain some information from each customer. Examples of the information you may provide us with include: name, postal address, e-mail address, and phone number.
We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our website. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer, and technical information about users’ means of connection to our website, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers’ utilized and other similar information.
We do not sell, rent or loan any identifiable information (such as e-mail address, phone number, etc.) regarding our customers to anybody. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates, and advertisers for the purposes outlined below. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the website or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. Any information you provide us with will be used responsibly, and is held with the utmost care and security.
Web Browser Cookies: Our website may use "cookies" to enhance user experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of our website may not function properly.
How We Use Collected Information: 3WISHES.COM collects and uses user personal information for the following purposes:• To Improve Customer ServiceYour information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.• To Personalize User ExperienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our website.• To Improve Our WebsiteWe continually strive to improve our website offerings and your satisfaction based on the information and feedback we receive from you.• To Process TransactionsWe may use the information users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.• To Administer a Content, Promotion, Survey or other Website FeatureTo send users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.• To Send Periodic EmailsThe email address users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If users decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Your Control over Your Information: If at any time you wish to opt out of our promotional emails, we provide the option to unsubscribe by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each email sent out. If at any time you wish to change or delete your personal information on your 3WISHES.COM membership account, you can either 1) login into your account with your username and password under My Account and change your personal information or 2) Contact us at 1-800-438-6605 or support@3wishes.com for our experienced staff to change or delete your personal information.
Guarantee
3WISHES.COM 100% Safe Shopping Guarantee.At 3WISHES.COM we want our customers to know they can shop with no worries. That's why we back every credit card purchase with our 100% Safe Shopping Guarantee. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at 3WISHES.COM. We use every resource and ability we have on hand to prevent this type of fraudulent behavior, because securing your personal information for a better shopping experience is our top priority.Guarantee details: Under the Fair Credit Billing Act your bank cannot hold you liable for more than fifty dollars worth of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this fifty dollars, 3WISHES.COM will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full fifty dollars. 3WISHES.COM will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at 3WISHES.COM while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. Also, to further safeguard your funds promptly notify 3WISHES.COM so we may return your funds to you in a timely manner.Our number one concern is our customer satisfaction, and we take our customers’ privacy very seriously. At 3WISHES.COM your private information is kept safe and secure because we have the appropriate staff, technology, and procedures to ensure we properly safeguard your information.Security
Safety in our Personnel: Each 3WISHES.COM staff member is appropriately trained and updated about preventing, detecting, and monitoring fraudulent behavior. At 3WISHES.COM we set the tone at the top that securing customers’ personal information is not only our duty, but is our commitment to our customers that they are in trusted hands. We ensure that the right controls are in place each step of the sales order process because we are dedicated to bringing our customers’ a safe, worry-free, shopping experience.Safety in our Technology: Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. At 3WISHES.COM we seek to constantly improve our information technology security as fraudulent behavior seeks to become more elusive. Management reviews what types of information technology security can be improved, remodeled, and implemented to ensure our customers’ personal data is well protected.Safety in our Procedures: At 3WISHES.COM we take a dynamic approach to evaluating the data security implemented in our procedures. When our Employees or Security Applications detect even a hint of fraudulent activity, it is sent for a multi-level review. If our procedures conclude that there is significant risks with an order, we will contact our customers to assure it is not fraudulent activity. Through both information system and manual controls we minimize risks to guarantee our customers’ safe, shopping experience.Compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act: Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to 3WISHES.COM. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.Third Party Websites: Users may find advertising or other content on our website that link to the websites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these websites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website. In addition, these websites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These websites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our website, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.Changes to this Privacy & Security Policy: 3WISHES.COM has the discretion to update this Privacy & Security Policy at any time. When this policy is revised the updated date of the revision will display at the bottom of this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your Acceptance of these Terms: By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.For any questions or concerns please contact us at 1-800-438-6605 or support@3wishes.com.
×
OK
© 2020 3wishes.com. All rights reserved | Sitemap
